jonasbrothersfanfictionarchive.com 2018-10-23

# Jonas Brothers Fanfiction Archive :: Your #1 source for Jonas Brothers Fan Fiction

Privacy Policy

A. Introduction

The privacy of our website visitors is very important to us, and we are committed to safeguarding it. This policy explains what we will do with your personal information.

Consenting to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first visit our website permits us to use cookies every time you visit our website.

B. Collecting personal information

The following types of personal information may be collected, stored, and used:

information about your computer including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, and operating system;

information about your visits to and use of this website including the referral source, length of visit, page views, and website navigation paths;

information, such as your email address, that you enter when you register with our website;

information that you enter when you create a profile on our website—for example, your name, profile pictures, gender, birthday, relationship status, interests and hobbies, educational

information that you enter while using the services on our website;

information that is generated while using our website, including when, how often, and under what circumstances you use it;

information that you post to our website with the intention of publishing it on the internet, which includes your username, profile pictures, and the content of your posts;

information contained in any communications that you send to us by email or through our website, including its communication content and metadata;

any other personal information that you send to us.

C. Using your personal information

Personal information submitted to us through our website will be used for the purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the website. We may use your personal information for the following:

administering our website;

personalizing our website for you;

enabling your use of the services available on our website;

sending you non-marketing commercial communications;

sending you email notifications that you have specifically requested;

providing third parties with statistical information about our users (but those third parties will not be able to identify any individual user from that information);

dealing with inquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to our website;

keeping our website secure and prevent fraud;

verifying compliance with the terms and conditions governing the use of our website (including monitoring private messages sent through our website private messaging service); and

other uses.

If you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We will not, without your express consent, supply your personal information to any third party for their or any other third party’s direct marketing.

D. Disclosing personal information

We may disclose your personal information to any of staff as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy.

We may disclose your personal information:

to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;

Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information to third parties.

E. International data transfers

Information that we collect will be stored and processed in the USA

Personal information that you publish on our website or submit for publication on our website may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others.

You expressly agree to the transfers of personal information described in this Section.

F. Retaining personal information

This Section sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations regarding the retention and deletion of personal information.

Notwithstanding the other provisions of this Section G, we will retain documents (including electronic documents) containing personal data:

to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

if we believe that the documents may be relevant to any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings; and

in order to establish, exercise, or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk).

G. Security of your personal information

We will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall-protected) servers.

All electronic financial transactions entered into through our website will be protected by encryption technology.

You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping the password you use for accessing our website confidential; we will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to our website).

H. Amendments

We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you understand any changes to this policy. We may notify you of changes to this policy by email or through the private messaging system on our website.

I. Your rights

If you reside in certain territories, including the EU, you have a number of rights in relation to your personal information. While some of these rights apply generally, certain rights apply only in certain limited cases. I describe these rights below:

\- Access. You may have the right to access and receive a copy of the personal information I hold about you by contacting me using the contact information below.

\- Change, restrict, delete. You may also have rights to change, restrict my use of, or delete your personal information. Absent exceptional circumstances (such as compliance with USA law) I will delete your personal information upon request.

\- Object. You can object to (i) my processing of some of your information based on my legitimate interests and (ii) receiving marketing messages from me after providing your express consent to receive them. In such cases, I will delete your personal information unless I have compelling and legitimate grounds to continue using that information or if it is needed for legal reasons.

\- Complain. If you reside in the EU and wish to raise a concern about my use of your information (and without prejudice to any other rights you may have), you have the right to do so with your local data protection authority.

J. Third party websites

Our website includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party websites. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies and practices of third parties.

K. Updating Infoamation

Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

L. Cookies

Our website uses cookies. A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. {SELECT ACCURATE PHRASING We use only session cookies / only persistent cookies / both session and persistent cookies on our website.}

The names of the cookies that we use on our website, and the purposes for which they are used, are set out below:

we use Google Analytics to collect usage data including browser, visit time and pages visited

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on justinbieberfanfictionplus.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Googles DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (interest based targeting).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).  DART uses non personally identifiable information  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visitingÂ http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies—for example:

in Internet Explorer (version 10) you can block cookies using the cookie handling override settings available by clicking “Tools,” “Internet Options,” “Privacy,” and then “Advanced”;

in Firefox (version 24) you can block all cookies by clicking “Tools,” “Options,” “Privacy,” selecting “Use custom settings for history” from the drop-down menu, and unticking “Accept cookies from sites”; and

in Chrome (version 29), you can block all cookies by accessing the “Customize and control” menu, and clicking “Settings,” “Show advanced settings,” and “Content settings,” and then selecting “Block sites from setting any data” under the “Cookies” heading.

Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites. If you block cookies, you will not be able to use all the features on our website.

You can delete cookies already stored on your computer—for example:

in Internet Explorer (version 10), you must manually delete cookie files (you can find instructions for doing so at http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835 );

in Firefox (version 24), you can delete cookies by clicking “Tools,” “Options,” and “Privacy”, then selecting “Use custom settings for history”, clicking “Show Cookies,” and then clicking “Remove All Cookies”; and

in Chrome (version 29), you can delete all cookies by accessing the “Customize and control” menu, and clicking “Settings,” “Show advanced settings,” and “Clear browsing data,” and then selecting “Delete cookies and other site and plug-in data” before clicking “Clear browsing data.”

Deleting cookies will have a negative impact on the usability of many websites

N. Contact

For purposes of EU data protection law, the JBFF staff acts as the the data controller of your personal information. If you have any questions or concerns, you may contact us at jbfastaff@gmail.com

To request delection of your information, please use this form. https://goo.gl/forms/212PQzWUsPBXXLth1
